Wedding Bells is a tv movie, romance film directed by Gary Yates.
Nick and Molly, commitment-phobic and busy professionals with little in common, are asked to be the
best man and maid of honor at the wedding of their mutual friends, Amy and Jamie.
Molly Quinn, played by Danica McKellar.
Nick Turner, played by Kavan Smith.
Amy Nelson, played by Tammy Gillis.
Charlie Turner, played by Bruce Boxleitner.
James, played by Christopher Russell.
Waiter, played by James Challis.
The People We Hate at the Wedding is a 2022 American romantic comedy film directed by Claire Scanlon from a
screenplay by the Molyneux sisters, based on the 2016 novel of the same name by Grant Ginder.
The film stars Allison Janney, Ben Platt, Cynthia
Addai-Robinson, and Kristen Bell.
The People We Hate at the Wedding was released on
Amazon Prime Video on November 18, 2022.
The tone is emotional.